Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records and Photographs WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series III: Records of the Professional Staff Congress, 1926-2009
  - Subseries III:D: Benefits-Related Files, 1972-1995
    - Benefits: Pension Transfers (ERS-TRS) - Cases, etc., 1973-1979 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Benefits: Pension/Welfare Benefits Memos, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Benefits: Pension/Welfare Benefits Memos, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Benefits: Pension/Welfare Benefits Memos, 1976-1982 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Benefits: Research Foundation, 1972-1982 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Benefits: Tax-Deferred Annuities, 1980-1986 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1983, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Employment Retirement Income Security Act (ERISA), 1974-1981 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Health Plan: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Health Plan: Correspondence, 1984-1990 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Health Plan Re-Opener, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Health Plan Transfers, undated, 1978-1981 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Pension Committee: General, 1973-1978, 1980-1986 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Pension Committee: Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Pension Committee: Meetings, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Pension Committee: Meetings, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Pension Committee: Meetings, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Pension Committee: Meetings, 1982, 1985-1987 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Pension Committee: Minutes, 1973-1979 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Pension Committee: Minutes, 1982-1986 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Pension Handbook, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Pension Supplementation Bill, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Pension Watchdog Committee, undated (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Retirement, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Retirement: Correspondence, 1972-1982 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Retirement: Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Retirement: Early Retirement, 1981-1992 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Retirement: Horowitz Case, 1982-1983 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Retirement: Horowitz Case, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Retirement Incentive Act, 1990, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Retirement: Mandatory, 1972-1990 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Retirement Plan Options, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Retirement Planning: "Ready or Not" Programs, undated, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Retirement Planning: "Ready or Not" Programs, 1981-1984 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Retirement Planning: "Ready or Not" Programs, 1985-1989 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Retirement: Second Careers, 1983-1984 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Retirement: Sullivan Study, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Tax Prep Transfer, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Tax Proposals: Federal, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Teachers' Insurance & Annuity Association (TIAA), 1984-1994 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - TIAA: Bindler Case, 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - TIAA: Disability, 1981-1984 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Unemployment Benefits, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Weinberg, Beryl: Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Weinberg, Beryl: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Weinberg, Beryl: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Weinberg, Beryl: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Weinberg, Beryl: Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Welfare Committee (Ad Hoc), 1978 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Welfare Fund, undated, 1972-1983 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Welfare Fund, 1984-1993 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Welfare Fund: Agreements and Proposals, undated, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Welfare Fund: Analysis and Recommendations, undated, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Welfare Fund: Annual Report, 1972-1982 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Welfare Fund: Background Material, 1974-1978 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Welfare Fund: Complaints and Comments, 1984-1987 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Welfare Fund: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Welfare Fund: Executive Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Welfare Fund: Financial Statements, 1976-1978 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Welfare Fund: Financial Statements, 1979-1980, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Welfare Fund: Forum, 1985-1989, 1992-1995 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Welfare Fund: Kinzel Commission, 1973-1976 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Welfare Fund: Members Correspondence, 1974-1985 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Welfare Fund: Resolutions, 1978-1980 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Welfare Fund: Retrenchment, 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Welfare Fund: Trustees Meetings, 1980-1985 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Arbitrations (CLOSED)
  - Abrams, A. Chang, L. (Box 75)
  - Chang L. (Box 76)
  - Hodys Hurewitz, P. (Box 77)
  - Hurewitz, P. Jansons, A. (Box 78)
  - Janus, S. (Box 79)
  - Jimenez, R. Kadragic, A. (Box 80)
  - Kaim, F. Kropp, N. (Box 81)
  - Kugler, I. Lervold, A. (Box 82)
  - Levine, E. - Levitt (Box 83)
  - Levy Long, W. (Box 84)
  - Lorber, S. (Box 85)
  - Lovell Lynch, C. (Box 86)
  - Lynes, G. Maged & Roth (Box 87)
  - Malz Matthew, D. (Box 88)
  - Mayhew, R. Minkoff, P. (Box 89)
  - Moetzinger, C. Mora, G. (Box 90)
  - Morpurgo, A. Moskowitz, C. (Box 91)
  - Motz, L. O'Conner (Box 92)
  - Oppelt, R. Paz, S. (Box 93)
  - Peck, N. Peton, F. (Box 94)
  - Polansky, M. PSC v. CUNY (adjunct pay) (Box 95)
  - PSC v. CUNY (various) (Box 96)
  - PSC v. MCC Raelson, J. (Box 97)
  - Ramjerdi, H. (Box 98)
  - Reese, S. Robinson, B. (Box 99)
  - Rodriguez, H. Rodriguez-Abad, L (Box 100)
  - Rokagh A. Rosenthal, A. (Box 101)
  - Ross, L. Rustin, S. (Box 102)
  - Ryan, N. Schlesinger, Y. (Box 103)
  - Schnall, D. Schwartz, L. (Box 104)
  - Seidman, S. Simon (Box 105)
  - Simonetti, B. Solomon, E. (Box 106)
  - Spalter, M. Storer, C. (Box 107)
  - Sussna, S. Thaxton, N. (Box 108)
  - Thomson, G. Torres, C. (Box 109)
  - Torres Del Valle, M. Valdes, M. (Box 110)
  - Varo, C. Viano R. (Box 111)
  - Viano, R. Vlahovic, A. (Box 112)
  - Vollmer, P. Voorsanger, L. (Box 113)
  - Williams, T. Wrong, E. (Box 114)
  - Yeakey, L. Ying, M. (Box 115)
- Series V: Addendum, 1957-2004
  Series V: Addendum, is comprised mostly of material donated by the union in 2006 after its headquarters was moved from 25 West 43rd St. in New York City. The series consists of six sub-series, as follows: A. Minutes, 1970-2004, including minutes of Delegate Assembly and Executive Council meetings; B. Correspondence, 1976-2000, including incoming and outgoing correspondence of Frank Annunziato, Barbara Bowen, Arnold Cantor, and Irwin Polishook; C. Bargaining Files, 1969-1995; D. City University of New York (CUNY), Budget and General Files, 1973-1999, including incoming and outgoing correspondence with CUNY officials, reports, budget materials, clippings and publicity material covering all aspects of the PSC's relationship with the CUNY system; E. Clarion Files, 1974-2000, including drafts of articles, editorial correspondence and background materials used in the production of the union's newspaper; F. General Files, 1957-2004, comprised of subject files on topics, organizations, persons and issues of concern to the union. Also included in this series are the files of the Belle Zeller Scholarship Fund, files on the PSC's relations with the American Association of University Professors (AAUP) and with the American Federation of Teachers, and extensive files documenting the activities of PSC chapters on the many campuses of the CUNY system.
  - Subseries A: Minutes, 1970-2004.
    - Delegate Assembly, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Delegate Assembly (I), 1973 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Delegate Assembly (II), 1973 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Delegate Assembly (III), 1973 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Delegate Assembly (I), 1974 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Delegate Assembly (II), 1974 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Delegate Assembly (I), 1975 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Delegate Assembly (II), 1975 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Delegate Assembly (I), 1976 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Delegate Assembly (II), 1976 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Delegate Assembly (I), 1977 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Delegate Assembly (II), 1977 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Delegate Assembly (I), 1978 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Delegate Assembly (II), 1978 (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Delegate Assembly (I), 1979 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Delegate Assembly (II), 1979 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1980 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1981 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1982 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1983 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Delegate Assembly (I), 1984 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Delegate Assembly (II), 1984 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Delegate Assembly (I), 1985 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Delegate Assembly (II), 1985 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Delegate Assembly (I), 1987 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Delegate Assembly (II), 1987 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Delegate Assembly (I), 1988 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Delegate Assembly (II), 1988 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1989 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Delegate Assembly, 2000-2002 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Delegate Assembly, 2003-2004 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Executive Council, 1970-1972 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Executive Council, Sep 4, 1973-Oct 18, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Executive Council, Oct 31, 1973-Feb 28, 1974 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Executive Council, Mar 7, 1974-Aug 13, 1974 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Executive Council, Sep 12, 1974-Mar 27, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Executive Council, May 1, 1975-Sep 9, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Executive Council, Sep 25, 1975-Jun 15, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Executive Council, Jul 1, 1976-Dec 28, 1976 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Executive Council, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Executive Council (I), 1978 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Executive Council (II), 1978 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Executive Council (I), 1979 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Executive Council (II), 1979 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Executive Council (I), 1980 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Executive Council (II), 1980 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Executive Council, 1981 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Executive Council (I), 1982 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Executive Council (II), 1982 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Executive Council, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Executive Council (I), 1984 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Executive Council (II), 1984 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Executive Council (I), 1985 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Executive Council (II), 1985 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Executive Council (I), 1986 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Executive Council (II), 1986 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Executive Council (I), 1987 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Executive Council (II), 1987 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Executive Council, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Executive Council, 1989 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence, 1976-2000.
    - Annunziato, Frank, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Annunziato, Frank, 1997 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Annunziato, Frank, 1998 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Annunziato, Frank, 1999 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Annunziato, Frank, 2000 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Bowen, Barbara, 2000 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1976-1977 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Cantor, Arnold, Jan 1979-May 1979 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Cantor, Arnold, Jun 1979-Dec 1979 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1983 (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1985-1986 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1989 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1990 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1991-1992 (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1993 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Cantor, Arnold, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1982-1983 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Jan 1984-Apr 1984 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Polishook, Irwin, May 1984-Aug 1984 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Sep 1984-Oct 1984 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Nov 1984-Dec 1984 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Jan 1985 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Feb 1985 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Mar 1985-Apr 1985 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Polishook, Irwin, May 1985-Jun 1985 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Jul 1985-Aug 1985 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Sep 1985-Oct 1985 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Nov 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Jan 1986-Mar 1986 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Apr 1986-May 1986 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Jun 1986-Aug 1986 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Sep 1986-Oct 1986 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Nov 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Jan 1987-Feb 1987 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Mar 1987-Apr 1987 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Polishook, Irwin, May 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Jan 1989-Mar 1989 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Apr 1989-May 1989 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Jun 1989-Sep 1989 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Oct 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Jan 1990-Feb 1990 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Mar 1990-Apr 1990 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Polishook, Irwin, May 1990-Aug 1990 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Sep 1990-Dec 1990 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Jan 1991-Mar 1991 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Apr 1991-Jul 1991 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Polishook, Irwin, Aug 1991-Dec 1991 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1992 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1994-1995 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1996-1997 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1998-2000 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Subseries C: Bargaining Files, 1969-1995.
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, 1969-1971 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, Feb 1972-Jun 1972 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, Jul 1972-Aug 1972 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, Sep 1972 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, Oct 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, Jan 1973-Apr 1973 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, May 1973 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, Jun 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, 1975 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, 1976 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, 1977 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, 1978 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Bargaining/Negotiations, 1980 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Contract Administration, 1986-1987 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Contract Administration, Jun 1991-Dec 1991 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Contract Administration, Jan 1992-May 1992 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Contract Administration, Jun 1992-Dec 1992 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Contract Administration, Jan 1993-Feb 1993 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Contract Administration, Mar 1993-Apr 1993 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Contract Administration, May 1993 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Contract Administration, Jun 1993 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Contract Administration, Jul 1993-Aug 1993 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Contract Administration, Sep 1993-Oct 1993 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Contract Administration, Nov 1993-Dec 1993 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Contract Administration, Jan 1994-Feb 1994 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Contract Administration, Mar 1994-Apr 1994 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Contract Administration, May 1994-Jun 1994 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Contract Administration, Jul 1994-Aug 1994 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Contract Administration, Sep 1994-Oct 1994 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Contract Administration, Nov 1994-Dec 1994 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Contract Administration, Jan 1995-Feb 1995 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Contract Administration, Mar 1995-Apr 1995 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Contract Administration, May 1995-Jun 1995 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Contract Administration, Jul 1995-Sep 1995 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Contract Administration, Oct 1995 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Contract Administration, Nov 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Subseries D: City University of New York (CUNY), Budget and General Files, 1973-1999.
    - Alumni, 1978-1995 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Associate Degree Program w/ John Jay College, 1991-1992 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Budget (I), Oct 1995 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Budget (II), Oct 1995 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Budget, Nov 1995 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Budget (I), Dec 1995 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Budget (II), Dec 1995 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Budget (I), 1995-1996 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Budget (II), 1995-1996 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Budget-Advertising, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Budget-Chancellors Request, 1989-1990 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Budget-Chancellors Request, 1990-1991 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Budget-Chancellors Request, 1991-1992 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Budget-Chancellors Request, 1992-1993 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Budget-Chancellors Request, 1993-1994 (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Budget-CUNY Legislative Action Council (CLAC), 1988-1989 (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - Budget-CLAC, 1995-1996 (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - Budget-Co-Affiliates, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Budget-Clarion, 1986-1987 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Budget-Clippings and Testimony, 1995-1996 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Budget-Community Colleges, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Budget-Executive Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Budget-Governors Report, 1985-1986 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Budget-Governors Report, 1988-1989 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Budget-Legislation, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Budget-Lobbying, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Budget-Lobbying, 1990-1991 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Budget-Lobbying, 1992-1993 (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Budget-Lobbying, 1995-1996 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Budget-Management, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Budget-Midyear Cuts, 1990-1991 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Budget-New York City, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Budget-New York City, 1990-1991 (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Budget-New York City, 1992-1993 (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Budget-New York City, 1994-1995 (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Budget-New York City (I), 1995-1996 (Box 129, Folder 19)
    - Budget-New York City (II), 1995-1996 (Box 129, Folder 20)
    - Budget-New York State United Teachers, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 21)
    - Budget-Professional Staff Congress, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 22)
    - Budget-Publicity, 1995-1996 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Budget-Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Budget-Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Budget-Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Budget-Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Budget-Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Budget-Requests, 1985-1986 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Budget-Requests, 1987-1988 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Budget-Speeches/Statements, 1989-1990 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Budget-State, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Budget-State, 1988-1989 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Budget-State (I), 1989-1990 (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Budget-State (II), 1989-1990 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Budget-State, 1990-1991 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Budget-State (I), 1992-1993 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Budget-State (II), 1992-1993 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Budget-State, 1994-1995 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Budget-State, 1995-1996 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Budget-State, Tax Cut, 1989 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Budget-State University of New York (SUNY), 1989-1990 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Budget-Student Protests, 1995-1996 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Budget-University Budget Office Report, 1993-1994 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Bylaws-Board of Directors, 1980 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Calendar, 1984-1986 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Calendar, 1987-1988 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Calendar, 1988-1989 (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Calendar, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Calendar, 1992-1993 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Calendar, 1993-1994 (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Calendar, 1994-1995 (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Calendar, 1995-1996 (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - Calendar, 1996-1997 (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Catalog Requests, 1982-1998 (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - Caucus of Employees with Disabilities, 1998 (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Chancellor, 1990-1998 (Box 131, Folder 20)
    - Clarion Committee, 1976-1983 (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - Collaborative Programs, 1985-1995 (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - College Prep Initiative, 1992-1995 (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Community Colleges, 1976-1989 (Box 131, Folder 24)
    - Community Colleges, 1997 (Box 131, Folder 25)
    - Compensatory Education Program (SEEK), 1983-1995 (Box 131, Folder 26)
    - Conferences, 1990-1996 (Box 131, Folder 27)
    - Consolidation Plans, 1992-1994 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Construction, 1995-1998 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Continuing Education, 1986-1987 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Curriculum, 1991-1997 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Distinguished Professors, 1985-1997 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Dorm Authority, 1997 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Enrollment (I), 1973-1996 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Enrollment (II), 1973-1996 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Ethnic Studies, 1993 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Facilities, 1989-1997 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Faculty, 1986-1999 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Development Program, 1981-1988 (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Exchange, 1985-1986 (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Funding, 1993-1994 (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - General Information, 1976-1983 (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - General Information, 1992-1996 (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - General Information, 1997 (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - General Information, 1998 (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - Grades, 1990 (Box 132, Folder 19)
    - Government Internship Program, 1993-1994 (Box 132, Folder 20)
    - History, 1925-1993 (Box 132, Folder 21)
    - Immigration, 1995 (Box 132, Folder 22)
    - Instructional Resource Center, 1986-1994 (Box 132, Folder 23)
    - Law School, 1979-1997 (Box 132, Folder 24)
    - Legislative-Welfare Fund, 1985 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Management, 1981-1998 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Management (I), 1988-1997 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Management (II), 1988-1997 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Master Plans, 1978-1992 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Medical School, 1985-1999 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Obituaries, 1992-1998 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Office of Administrative Services, 1987-1997 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Open Admissions (I), 1968-1998 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Open Admissions (II), 1968-1998 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Pensions, 1997 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases (I), 1982-1995 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Press Releases (II), 1982-1995 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Press Releases (III), 1982-1995 (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Programs, 1978-1999 (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Publications, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - Remediation, 1998-1999 (Box 133, Folder 17)
    - Retrenchment (I), 1995 (Box 133, Folder 18)
    - Retrenchment (II), 1995 (Box 133, Folder 19)
    - Retrenchment Guidelines, 1992-1995 (Box 133, Folder 20)